and.co 2019-06-21

# Privacy Policy | AND CO

Last updated: November 2018 

Fiverr International Ltd. and its affiliates (including Fiverr Inc.) (“Fiverr” or “we”) takes privacy very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your information in connection with Your use of AND CO’s Services, Website, and App (“And Co”). We receive information about You from various sources, including without limitation: (i) if You register for the Services, through Your user account (your “Account”); (ii) Your use of the Services, Website, and App generally; and (iii) from third party websites and services. When You use the Services, You are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of Your information as described in this Privacy Policy. We encourage You to read this privacy policy (“Policy”) carefully. It will help You make informed decisions about sharing Your Personal Information with us.

The defined terms in this Privacy Policy, if not defined herein, shall have the same meaning as in AND CO’s Terms of Service, available at <https://www.and.co/terms> (the “Terms of Service,” and together with the Privacy Policy, the “Terms”), which You should read together with this Privacy Policy before accessing or using the Services. By accessing and using our Services, You consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and agree to be bound by it and our Terms.

## We collect Your Personal Information:

AND CO is a platform for online back office service designed for freelancers and small businesses, including online accounting and finance management application and services, simple contract and document template services, and professional referral services. The information we gather enables us to personalize, improve and continue to operate the Services. In connection with certain aspects of the Services, we may request, collect and/or display some of your Personal Information. “Personal Information” is information about an identifiable individual, and may include information such as the individual’s name, email address, telephone number, bank account details, taxation details, and accounting and financial information. We may collect Personal Information directly from You when You:

  * register to use the Services through Your user account (your “Account”),
  * use the Services,
  * post to the AND CO Community forum or on our blog,
  * contact the AND CO support team, and/or
  * visit our Website or App.

You can always choose not to provide us Your Personal Information, but it may mean that we are unable to provide You with the Services.

## We may receive Personal Information from You about others:

Through Your use of the Services, we may also collect information from You about someone else. If You provide us with Personal Information about someone else, You warrant and represent that You are authorized to disclose that information to us and that we may collect, use and disclose such information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

This means that You must take reasonable steps to ensure the individual concerned is aware of and/or consents to the various matters detailed in this Privacy Policy, including the fact that their Personal Information is being collected, the purposes for which that information is being collected, the intended recipients of that information, the individual's right to obtain access to that information, our identity, and how to contact us.

Where requested to do so by us, You must also assist us with any requests by the individual to access or update the Personal Information You have collected from them and entered into the Services.

## We collect, hold, and use Your Personal Information for limited purposes:

**We** collects Your Personal Information so that we can provide You with the Services. In doing so, we may use the Personal Information we have collected from You for purposes related to the Services, including but not limited to:

  * verify Your identity,
  * administer the Services,
  * notify You of new or changed services offered in relation to the Services,
  * carry out marketing or training relating to the Services,
  * assist with the resolution of technical support issues or other issues relating to the Services,
  * comply with applicable rules, laws and regulations, and
  * communicate with You.

By using the Services, You consent to Your Personal Information being collected, held and used in this way and for any other use You authorize. We will only use Your Personal Information for the purposes described in this Policy or in accordance with Your express consent.

Note that we do not collect financial information, such as your bank account or credit card number, credit card type and expiration date, and other such information (“Financial Information”). When You register for your Account or pay Your invoices, Your Financial Information is collected and stored by our Payment Processor. Currently, our’s Payment Processor for payments for use of the Services is Stripe ([https://stripe.com](https://stripe.com/)). If you use Stripe, you agree to the Stripe terms of service (located at <https://stripe.com/payment-terms/legal>) and privacy policy (located at <https://stripe.com/us/privacy>).

## We may aggregate Your non-personally identifiable data:

By using the Services, You agree that we may access, aggregate and use non-personally identifiable data we have collected from You (“Non-Personal Information”). We may share Non-Personal information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business (“Business Partners”). Non-Personal information includes information that is (i) not Personal Information or (ii) derived from Personal Information but has been anonymized so that it is no longer personally identifiable. We use and share this type of data so that we and our Business Partners can understand how and how often people use our and their services or websites, which facilitates improving our Services, their services and how our Services interface with their services. In addition, these Business Partners may share with us non-private, aggregated or otherwise Non-Personal Information about You that they have independently developed or acquired.

## We may use Non-Personal Information to:

  * assist us to better understand how our customers are using the Services,
  * provide our customers with further information regarding the uses and benefits of the Services,
  * enhance freelancer’s productivity, including by creating useful business insights from that aggregated data and allowing You to benchmark Your business’ performance against that aggregated data, and
  * otherwise to improve the Services.

## Our Servers:

All data, including Personal and Non-Personal Information, that is entered into the Services by You, or automatically imported on Your instruction, is transferred to our servers as a function of transmission across the Internet. By using the Services, You consent to Your Personal Information being transferred to our servers as set out in this Privacy Policy.

You should review our Privacy Policy regularly to keep informed of any updates.

## Steps We Take to protect your Personal Information:

**We are** committed to protecting the security of Your Personal Information and we take all reasonable, industry-standard precautions to protect it from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers and all data transferred between You and the Services is encrypted. However, the Internet is not in itself a secure environment and we cannot give an absolute assurance that Your Personal Information will be secure at all times. Transmission of Personal Information over the Internet is at Your own risk and You should only input, or instruct the inputting of, Personal Information to the Services within a secure environment. You are responsible for preventing unauthorized access to Your account and Personal Information, including, for example, by protecting Your account credentials and limiting access to devices on which You access the Services.

We will advise You as soon as reasonably possible, and in accordance with applicable laws, upon discovering or being advised of a security breach where Your Personal Information is lost, stolen, accessed, used, disclosed, copied, modified, or disposed of by any unauthorized persons or in any unauthorized manner.

## We only discloses Your Personal Information in limited circumstances:

We will only disclose the Personal Information You have provided to us to entities outside the Fiverr group of companies if it is necessary and appropriate to facilitate the purpose for which Your Personal Information was collected pursuant to this Privacy Policy, including the provision of the Services. We will not otherwise disclose Your Personal Information to a third party unless You have provided Your express consent. However, notwithstanding the foregoing, we does reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as we reasonably believe is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; (ii) enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof; (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (iv) respond to user support requests or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention. Where possible and appropriate, we will notify You if we are required by law to disclose Your Personal Information.

We may employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our control (our “Agents”). We may need to share Personal Information with our Agents in order to provide the Services to You. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Your Personal Information with our Agents.

Finally, We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use Your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

## You may request access to Your Personal Information:

It is Your responsibility to ensure that the Personal Information You provide to us is accurate, complete and up-to-date. You may request access to the Personal Information we hold about You, or request that we update or correct any Personal Information we hold about You, by setting out Your request in writing and sending it to us at [hello@andco.nyc](mailto:hello@andco.nyc).

We will process Your request as soon as reasonably practicable, provided we are not otherwise prevented from doing so on legal grounds. If we are unable to meet Your request, we will let you know why. In some circumstances, it may be necessary for us to seek to arrange access to Your Personal Information through a mutually agreed intermediary (for example, the Subscriber).

We’ll only keep Your Personal Information for as long as we require it for the purposes of providing You with the Services. However, we may also be required to keep some of Your Personal Information for specified periods of time, for example under certain laws relating to corporations, money laundering, and financial reporting legislation.

## Rights of Users Under EU Regulation

Under applicable EU regulation, as of May 25, 2018 you may have some or all of the following rights in addition to the rights listed above in respect of your Personal Information:

  1. to obtain a copy of your Personal Information together with information about how and on what basis that Personal Information is processed;
  2. to rectify inaccurate Personal Information;
  3. to erase your Personal Information in limited circumstances where it is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which it was collected or processed;
  4. to restrict processing of your Personal Information where: (a) the accuracy of the Personal Information is contested; (b) the processing is unlawful but you object to the erasure of the Personal Information; (c) we no longer require the Personal Information for the purposes for which it was collected, but it is required for the establishment, exercise or defense of a legal claim;
  5. to challenge processing which we have justified on the basis of our legitimate interest;
  6. to object to decisions which are based solely on automated processing or profiling;
  7. to obtain a portable copy of your Personal Information, or to have a copy transferred to a third party controller; or
  8. to obtain a copy of or access to safeguards under which your Personal Information is transferred outside of the EEA.

In addition to the above, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority for data protection.

We may ask you for additional data to confirm your identity and for security purposes, before disclosing data requested to you. We reserve the right to charge a fee where permitted by law. We may also decline to process requests that jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or would cause us to take any action that is not permissible under applicable laws. Additionally, as permitted by applicable laws, we may need to retain certain personal information for a longer period of time for recordkeeping purposes, such as retaining records relating to your transactions for warranty or accounting purposes.

## California Privacy Rights:

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: 285 West Broadway, Suite 430, New York, NY 10013.

## use of cookies:

In providing the Services, we utilizes "cookies." A cookie is a small text file that is stored on Your computer for record-keeping purposes. A cookie does not identify You personally or contain any other information about You but it does identify Your computer.

We and some of our affiliates and third-party service providers may use a combination of “persistent cookies” (cookies that remain on Your hard drive for an extended period of time) and “session ID cookies” (cookies that expire when You close Your browser) on the Website to, for example, track overall site usage, and track and report on Your use and interaction with ad impressions and ad services.

You can set your browser to notify You when You receive a cookie so that You will have an opportunity to either accept or reject it in each instance. However, You should note that refusing cookies may have a negative impact on the functionality and usability of the Website.

## You can opt-out of any email communications:

**We** send billing information, product information, Services updates and Services notifications to You via email. Our emails will contain clear and obvious instructions describing how You can choose to be removed from any mailing list not essential to the Services. We will remove You at Your request. Please read the applicable unsubscribe instructions carefully. Please note that requesting to be removed from one mailing list may not result in Your being removed from all mailing lists to which You are subscribed. You may need to send separate requests to be removed from each specific mailing list to which You are subscribed.

## You are responsible for transfer of Your data to third-party applications:

The Services may allow You, the Subscriber, or another Invited User within the relevant subscription to the Services to transfer data, including Your Personal Information, electronically to and from third-party websites, services and applications. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of such third parties that we do not own or control. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those third-party websites, services, and applications that share our respect for your privacy, we have no control over, and take no responsibility for, the privacy practices or content of these websites, services, and applications. You are responsible for checking the privacy policy of any such applications so that You can be informed of how they will handle Your Personal Information.

## Privacy complaints process:

If You have any questions or concerns regarding privacy in connection with the Services, Website, or App, or wish to complain about how we have handled Your Personal Information, please provide our Privacy Officer team with full details and any supporting documentation:

  * by e-mail at [hello@andco.nyc](mailto:hello@andco.nyc), or [DPO@Fiverr.com](mailto:DPO@Fiverr.com)
  * by letter to: 38 Greene St., New York, NY 10013, USA

We will endeavor to:

  * provide an initial response to Your query or complaint within 10 business days, and
  * investigate and attempt to resolve Your query or complaint within 30 business days or such longer period as is necessary and notified to you by our Privacy Officer.

## This policy may be updated from time to time:

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify You by posting an announcement on the Services or sending You an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.
